<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorized</title>
	<atom:link href="https://eduquer.byspirit.org/category/uncategorized/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://eduquer.byspirit.org/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 17:33:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>fr-FR</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://eduquer.byspirit.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/cropped-cropped-cropped-LogoESEfondclair-e1711641360853-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Uncategorized</title>
	<link>https://eduquer.byspirit.org/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Hello world!</title>
		<link>https://eduquer.byspirit.org/hello-world/</link>
					<comments>https://eduquer.byspirit.org/hello-world/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[eduquer-light]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 13:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://eduquer.byspirit.org/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing! “Compounding is the greatest mathematical discovery of all time.” — Albert Einstein The quest to become a better version of... <p class="more"><a class="more-link" href="https://eduquer.byspirit.org/hello-world/">Read More</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!</p>



<p id="1760"><em>“Compounding is the greatest mathematical discovery of all time.” — </em><strong><em>Albert Einstein</em></strong></p>



<p id="2159">The quest to become a better version of yourself often feels like a roller coaster ride. It’s hard. And it’s usually so uneven. You can end in failure. But life is a journey, not a marathon, so you always have another opportunity to restart and improve.</p>



<p id="e925">Many people practically look out for secrets, tricks, and hacks that will make EVERYTHING better right now. But unfortunately life doesn’t work that way. There are no “overnight successes”. Think of all the incredible people you truly admire. They didn’t succeed becasue of one giant move, but rather a series of small and consistent actions over time.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="034d">Stop aiming for radical personal&nbsp;change!</h3>



<p id="5d95"><em>“Be patient with yourself. Self-growth is tender; it’s holy ground. There’s no greater investment.” —</em><strong><em> Stephen Covey</em></strong></p>



<p id="421f">A magic bullet cannot save you! You’ve got to embrace the process and enjoy it. You can’t escape the hard work it takes to get better. Every incredibly successful person you know today has been through the boring, mundane, time-tested process that eventually brings success. So, stop looking for “quick hacks” that bring faster results.</p>



<p id="8ae3">Instead of reading every self-improvement post for the one golden tip that will make you superhumanly efficient, focus on doing the actual work that needs to be done. You can inspire yourself to take action. The hard, long process is the only way though. You can’t achieve tremendous life success with a quick fix. Nobody gets it that easy.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://eduquer.byspirit.org/hello-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
